♪ Ooh, you make me live ♪
♪ 哦  你让我活下去 ♪
♪ Whatever this world can give to me ♪
♪ 不管世界能给我什么 ♪
♪ It's you, you're all I see ♪
♪ 是你  我眼中只有你 ♪
♪ Ooh, you make me live now, honey ♪
♪ 哦  是你让我支撑到现在一直活下去  甜心 ♪
♪ Ooh, you make me live ♪
♪ 哦  是你让我活下去 ♪
♪ Oh, you're the best friend that I ever had ♪
♪ 哦  你是我有生以来最好的朋友 ♪
♪ I've been with you such a long time ♪
♪ 我们在一起生活了好久 ♪
♪ You're my sunshine ♪
♪ 你是我的阳光 ♪
♪ And I want you to know that my feelings are true ♪
♪ 我要你明白我是真心实意 ♪
♪ I really love you ♪
♪ 我真的爱你 ♪
♪ Oh, you're my best friend ♪
♪ 哦  你是我最好的朋友 ♪
♪ Ooh, you make me live ♪
♪ 哦  是你让我活下去 ♪
♪ Ooh, I've been wandering round ♪
♪ 哦  我一直四处游荡 ♪
♪ But I still come back to you ♪  ♪ Come back to you ♪
♪ 但我依然会回到你身边 ♪
♪ In rain or shine you've stood by me, girl ♪
♪ 不论阴晴圆缺  你始终陪伴左右  女孩 ♪
♪ I'm happy at home ♪  ♪ Happy at home ♪
♪ 我很高兴又回到了家 ♪
♪ You're my best friend ♪
♪ 你是我最好的朋友 ♪
♪ Ooh, you make me live ♪   ♪ Ooh ♪
♪ 哦  是你让我活下去 ♪
♪ Ooh, you're my best friend ♪
♪ 哦  你是我最好的朋友 ♪
♪ I was so tired of being upset ♪
♪ 我厌倦了心烦意乱 ♪
♪ Always wanted something I never could get ♪
♪ 总想要我得不到的东西 ♪
♪ Life's an illusion, love is a dream ♪
♪ 人生如同幻影  爱情有如梦境 ♪
♪ But I don't know what it is ♪
♪ 但我不清楚这是为何 ♪
♪ Everybody's happy nowadays ♪
♪ 如今人人快乐 ♪
♪ I was so tired of being upset ♪
♪ 我厌倦了心烦意乱 ♪
♪ Always wanted something I never could get ♪
♪ 总想要我得不到的东西 ♪
♪ Life's an illusion, love is a dream ♪
♪ 人生如同幻影  爱情有如梦境 ♪
♪ But I don't know what it is cos ♪
♪ 但我不清楚这是为何  因为…♪
♪ Everybody's happy nowadays ♪
♪ 如今人人快乐 ♪
♪ Life's an illusion, love is a dream ♪
♪ 人生如同幻影  爱情有如梦境 ♪
♪ But I don't know what it is ♪
♪ 但我不清楚这是为何 ♪
♪ Everybody's saying things to me ♪
♪ 人人对我说长论短 ♪
♪ But I know it's OK, OK ♪
♪ 但我一点儿也不介意 ♪
♪ Everybody's happy nowadays ♪
♪ 如今人人快乐 ♪
♪ Life's an illusion, love is a dream ♪
♪ 人生如同幻影  爱情有如梦境 ♪
♪ Everybody's happy nowadays ♪
♪ 如今人人快乐 ♪
♪ Days ♪
♪ 快乐日子 ♪
♪ Bet you are tired of being upset ♪
♪ 我敢说你厌倦了生气 ♪
♪ Always wanted something you never could get ♪
♪ 总想要你得不到的东西 ♪
♪ Life's no illusion, love's not a dream ♪
♪ 人生绝非幻影  爱情亦非梦境 ♪
♪ Now I know just what it is ♪
♪ 终于我明白了为何 ♪
♪ Everybody's happy nowadays ♪
♪ 如今人人快乐 ♪
♪ Days ♪
♪ 快乐日子 ♪